

# SOFTWARE ENGINEER/FULLSTACK.NET DEVELOPER

DAYÁN RUIZ

#### PROFILE

Software Enginner/Full Stack .NET Developer with more than five years of experience in web development. Passion for learning, coding, improve my skills and grow professionally.

Looking for new challenges and extremely motivated for being Head of Software Engineering.

### CONTACT

- Montevideo, Uruguay
- dayanrr91@gmail.com
- +598 93668048
- in /dayan-ruiz-riera

# SKILLS

C# ASP.NET MVC SQL

ASP.NET Web Api AngularJS

ReactJS JQuery Angular 2+

HTML CSS SCRUM SQL-Server

Entity Framework Dapper Git

# WORK EXPERIENCE

## **FullStack .NET Developer**

MIDDLESOFT | OCT 2019 - PRESENT

- Web development using C#, ASP.NET MVC, ASP.NET CORE, JQuery, SQL Server, HTML and CSS.
- Collaborate with web developer teams in architecture, backend and frontend tasks.
- Direct communication with clients, including demo and deploys.

#### **FullStack .NET Developer**

ONETREE | MAR 2017 - OCT 2019

- Web development using C#, ASP.NET MVC, AngularJS, SQL Server, HTML and CSS.
- Collaborate with web developer teams in architecture, backend and frontend tasks.
- Direct communication with clients, always in english.

#### **FRONTEND Developer - Part-time**

FREELANCER | APR 2019 - OCT 2019

- Frontend development using HTML, CSS, ReactJS and Redux.
- Collaborate with web developer teams in frontend tasks.
- Direct communication with clients.

#### EDUCATION

University of Informatics Sciences Software Engineer, 2019-2014

#### LANGUAGE

English: Advanced

Spanish: Native

#### **FRONTEND Developer - Part-time**

SOYUZLABS | JUN 2018 - DEC 2018

- Frontend development using HTML, CSS and Angular 6.
- Collaborate with web developer teams in architecture, and frontend tasks.

#### **FullStack .NET Developer**

SOPHILABS | MAY 2016 - MAR 2017

- Web development using C#, ASP.NET MVC, ASP.NET WebApi and SQL Server, HTML and CSS.
- Collaborate with web developer teams in backend and frontend tasks.

#### **Web Developer - Part-time**

UNIVERSIDAD DE LAS CIENCIAS INFORMÁTICAS | SEP 2014 - MAR 2016

- Using technologies like Java, Spring, HTML and CSS.
- Construction and maintainance of a monitoring module for an open source tool.
- Collaborate with web developer teams in backend and frontend tasks.